[Music]
in today's video we're going to be
carrying on with our shop system that
we've been working on you can see over
here we can go to our mpc here we can
see the players got 500 gold and the
shop has a thousand gold we've got cogs
we've got 99 cogs uh 150 health post
sorry 10 health potions there are 150 g
and there's one item which is 150 g if
we then click on these buttons here we
can add to our basket total we can
remove from our basket and you can see
that it's updating here if we add too
many items to the uh basket that we
can't afford so if we go over the
player's goal so the player is 500 gold
the basket totals 610 gold we can't
afford them if we hit the buy button
nothing's happening so let's just remove
um the potions from the basket total so
now we've got five cogs three health
potions and then we hit buy items you
can see that we've bought the items
the amount that we had in our baskets
gone into the shop gold and it's been
taken away from the player's gold and
then if i shut this panel you can see in
our inventory we've got the cogs and
potions here i'd already picked up some
potions from
the floor let's just drop them on the
ground um
let's drop the cogs on the ground let's
go over here press e
so let's uh buy some more cogs i'll buy
seven cogs close our inventory and you
can see that we've got seven cogs in our
inventory now we've got our full potions
which we bought earlier but that's what
we're going to do in this video let's
just jump straight into it
okay let's just jump straight into this
one then so we're going to work on
adding the functionality to add and
remove things
to the shopping cart
so the first thing we want to do is we
need to introduce a variable that's
going to keep track of like the
temporary count we don't want to
actually change the underlying
shop slot
what we want to do is have a private int
which we will call
temp oh
amount
and then when we set up the shop slot ui
and we assign everything here we're
going to set the temp amount equal to
the slot dot
stack size so now we can change
we can add and remove stuff to the car
but if we exit out of the interface
we're not going to have actually changed
the shop's uh inventory we're not going
to have removed anything from the shops
slots
until we actually press the buy button
once we press the buy button
then we'll actually take it from the
stack size so we're just creating this
temporary amount to keep track of that
so let's work on adding stuff to the car
first so with add item to cart
we want to just check to make sure that
there is actually an item to add to the
car so if our temp amount is greater
than zero then we're gonna remove an
item from the temp amount because going
into the cart
we're gonna call our parent display and
we're gonna um
add
item
to cart and we're just going to pass in
ourselves as this and we can make that
function there over on the
shopkeeper display script we're going to
have a add item to cart which takes in a
shop slot ui
and variable and we'll go back to our
shop slot ui script
and then we're just going to update the
um item count dot text is going to be
equal to our temp
amount dot 2 string
i'm going to invert that if so if it's
less than or equal to 0 then we're just
going to return and if not then we can
reduce
1 from the amount
add it to the cut
and then update the ui slot text
and then for the remove item from cart
we're just going to do the opposite so
if
temp amount is equal to the assigned
item slot dot stack size
and let's just return
because there's nothing to
we have
because if the temp amount's the same
then there's nothing in the car
so we we don't need to manipulate it
anyway so we can just remove and the
remove item button won't work it won't
do anything
um but
if the temp amount is different to the
actual amount of the shop slot then
we're just going to
increase our temporary amount
we're going to call parent display
remove
item from cart
again passing in ourselves
and then we're going to update the
itemcount.text
to the temp
amount.2string and again let's make this
method over on our shopkeeper display
so it's going to be remove item from
cart taking in a shop slot and that's on
the shopkeeper display script and for
now i'm just going to remove these
system exceptions
okay so if we go back over to unity
and we hit play
let's go over to one of our shops so you
can see that there's 99 bugs 10 health
potions and one sword item if we hit the
plus
this is going to start adding stuff to
the car and removing from the temporary
amount
if we actually check the mpc we haven't
changed the shop inventory we're not
going to do that until we actually press
buy because there's no guarantee that
the player would complete the purchase
they could press escape
and close this panel and then
go back to it and that we need the shop
to have been reset so we don't want to
actually change the shop inventory until
we've hit the buy button which is going
to be over here
and you can see that we can remove um
items from the car and we can go back up
to the original stack size but we can't
remove items that we don't have so we
can't go to 100 cogs and you know we can
do this all the way down to zero and we
can't add any more
than the shop inventory currently has
so now we need to actually change add
them to the car which is going to be
this window over here
let's go do that so let's go back over
to our
editor
and this is where it's going to be quite
confusing hopefully you'll follow along
and i'll try and explain everything as i
go so i'm gonna get a reference to the
data from the shop slot ui
and we'll get the
um assigned
i think we're gonna need to go through
the shop slot ui and
we need to make a public getter for this
um shop slot so we're going to make a
public
shop
slot
called assigned
item slot which will return our assigned
item slot
now back over on our shopkeeper display
we can get the assigned item slots item
data we can just cache that in this
variable which we're going to call data
and then um
here we will update the item preview
passing in our shop slot ui
again this is gonna be another method
we're not gonna we'll work on this later
but this is gonna be where it shows the
name and the description and the
thumbnail
and but we'll do that okay so we're now
going to use this uh shopping cart
dictionary that we made which remember
takes in an item data and an int so oh
here we're going to say if our shopping
cart
dot uh contains key
data so if our shopping cart already has
this data in it
and how do i stop that if we already
have the data in it so if this item is
already in our shopping cart then we are
going to add to the shopping cart one so
if the shopping cart already has it and
we're adding an item to the car we're
just going to increase the int in the
dictionary by one meaning that there's
going to be one more of that data in the
cart and then this is where the markups
gonna start to come in and the shop
markup so we're gonna do um make a new
variable called price and this is gonna
equal and i'm gonna make a new method
called get modified
right because this is going to we're
going to use this in a few different
places so we're going to pass in the
shop slot so
so to this we're going to add in the
data i'm going to add in an amount which
is just going to be one
in this case and then we'll do shop slot
ui dot
markup so this is going to be the markup
value
and let's make this method so this is
going to be a private static int again
called modified price which is going to
take in um some data and amount as well
as the markup here and all this is going
to do is we're going to
get the base value so base value is
equal to
the data dot val gold value times by our
amount so remember this gold value here
is what we define as the value of the
item so if the gold value is 100 and we
pass in
2 of the amount the base value before we
change it with the markup is going to be
200.
once we've calculated the base value we
can just return
the math f dot round two int
and we can do the base value
plus
the base value times by the markup let's
just see that math kind of in action so
so if we take our base value of
100 and we have one of them so the base
value is going to be 100
and then we have a markup
of 50 which is going to be 0.5 so 50 of
100 is 50
and then we're going to add that
to the base value so we're going to do
the base value times by the markup
that'll be done first and then it'll be
added to the base values that would be
it would be 50 plus 100 is 150 so that's
the markup and that'll work for sort of
you know any
and so if we do
a base value of um 75
there's a markup of 30
and then we add 75 back to that the
price is gonna be 97.5
and the reason we're rounding it to an
int is that obviously the price the gold
amount is an int we don't want point
five gold and so we're just going to
round that up so that's how we're going
to get our modified price and once we've
got this price
we can then make a new variable called
new string and we'll equal this to ring
that's got the shop slot it's got the
data dot display name and then i'm going
to put the price in brackets so we'll do
um price with a g
that's how much gold there's going to be
and then we'll pass in
from our dictionary the amount of that
data that we have so shopping cart at um
data so that's going to be the value so
that's going to be the int so it's going
to be display name
with the markup so you know a cog for
100 gold and it'll show that we've got
10 of them in the basket for example and
then remember we've also got the other
dictionary which is this shop the one
with the shopping cart item ui
in it which will correspond to this uh
bit of data here so we can go to our
shopping cart text shopping cart ui
dictionary we're going to get
the value the value with the key of our
data
and we're going to set item text
we're going to pass in our new string
now again this is another method we need
to make so let's create that method
this is over on our shopping cart item
ui which we've not fully set up any of
the variables yet so let's do that now
so
all this is going to have is a
serialized field private text mesh pro u
gui
and we'll call this item text and then
all we're going to do here is set
item text dot text equal to our new
string and that's actually set up this
prefab um in unity so let's go back over
to unity
and we've got our shopping cart item
prefab here with the shopping cart item
ui
script so we're just going to get the
script and drag the text into the
serialized field of the item text we'll
go back to our main scene here so that's
the shopping cart item ui script let's
jump back over to our shopkeeper display
script and here we're going to increase
the basket total
by the price so this is the current cost
of the basket
so basket total
plus equals
the
price
and then we can set the basket
total text to display that price so we
say total and then pass in our basket
total and that's the amount of gold that
the basket is currently going to cost so
this is if our shopping cart already
contains the key this is our shopping
cart this is if our shopping cart
already contains the data that we're
trying to add
if it isn't then we're going to need to
add to the dictionary and then do some
of this stuff so we can say
else shopping cart
dot add we can pass in the data and the
amount
so it's gonna be one in this case then
we're going to
instantiate
a new shopping cart text object and i'm
gonna
get a reference to this so we can modify
it so we're gonna instantiate and we're
gonna do the shopping cart shopping cart
item prefab and that's gonna be attached
to our shopping cart content panel um
transform we're going to get the
price and i'm actually going to just
copy that and i'll pop it outside of the
um
item cart
i'll pop it out
outside of this if statement and then we
can just use the price down here
um and we could actually do that with
new string as well here and we want to
set our shopping cart text obj and we're
gonna do set item text passing in our
new string and we want to add this
shopping cart text obj to our dictionary
that contains the text so
um
shopping cart ui dictionary
dot add and we'll pass in the shopping
cart text obj and that says the value we
need to pass in the data as the key and
then after that we can update the basket
total so again i'm just going to cut
that out and i'm going to paste place it
at the bottom here so that's just
cleared this script up and made it a bit
easier
in my test project i
seem to have a lot of duplicate code
hopefully this will work um so then once
the basket total is um calculated we can
say if the basket total
is greater than zero
and the basket total text
isn't active then we just want to enable
the basket total text and say um enabled
equals true and then we can set the buy
button to be true to be enabled as well
so gameobject.setactive
true and then finally we're going to
have a new another method called check
part first available gold and we'll
press
we'll make that method here so this is
going to be private void check cart
against
available gold and here we're going to
do um
a new variable gold to check and here we
want to see whether we're selling an
item or buying an item so to do that we
need to introduce a variable that's
keeping track of which kind of
buy mode
we're in are we in selling mode or buy
mode so we can just make a new bull and
i'll move this to the top in a second
i'm just going to put it here for now
um private bull
is
selling and we can say
are we
selling
if we are selling an item then we're
checking the shop system
dot available gold and if we're not
selling we need to check the player's
gold so we can do player inventory
holder
dot inventory system gold again we've
got those tabs that we set up the buy
and sell button if we're buying
when we add things from the shop system
to the cart and then we try and buy it
we need to make sure the player has
enough money
and then if we are selling items to the
shop we're going to add items from the
player's inventory to the shopping cart
and then when we click the sell button
we need to check to see if the shop has
enough gold to buy all of that so that's
what this is doing here um we'll use
this ball a bit later on
by default it's going to be false until
we set up the tabs
so this is going to be checking the
player's inventory um
for their gold amount and here we're
going to update the basket total text
dot color
i'm going to set that
either to um white or red depending on
whether the player has enough money just
as a bit of an indication that you've
gone over the sort of
the basket amount
so you've gone over the amount that the
player can actually afford to buy so we
can set the
color based on this um the basket total
is the basket total greater than the
amount of gold
that we that we currently have available
to us if it is greater
then we're going to set the color of the
text to red and this could be sort of
any color that you want that fits your
style and if we're if we do have enough
we're just going to set it to white and
obviously if it's already white it
won't change um so that's that for now
we'll be doing uh a bit more in this
method later on um when we set up the
selling mode but let's just focus on
getting uh buying items to work for now
okay so then we need to check as well um
as well as the available gold we need to
check to make sure the player inventory
has enough space in it to buy the um
to buy these items and if they don't we
can update the basket total text to say
something like not enough room in
inventory so let's make an if statement
here so if we are selling items to the
shop then
we can just return because we're not
going to um so we're selling items to
the shop then we don't care about this
step of you know checking uh the
inventory so we're gonna if we're
selling or
the player inventory holder our primary
inventory system
and then we're gonna make a new method
called check inventory
remaining and we're gonna pass in
our shopping cart dictionary so this is
going to be a method over on our
inventory system script and it's just
going to return a ball and we're going
to do some stuff to check whether
we have enough room in our inventory for
the um shopping cart to fit so to make
this work we're going to make a clone of
the current inventory system the
player's inventory and then we're going
to attempt to add all of the items from
the dictionary to that cloned inventory
system
if we get an error saying that the
inventory system is
full and we've we failed to add it then
we're just going to return false and if
we successfully get through that check
of on the clone system we'll return
true because there's obviously enough
room in the inventory to add all of this
stuff to the player's inventory so
if that doesn't make sense hopefully
it'll make more sense as we start to
clone
to code it i'm going to make a variable
called cloned system
and this is going to be equal to a new
inventory system and it's going to be of
the same size as
our current inventory size and then to
this cloned system we need to go into a
for loop and add all of our current
items to the cloned system so we say uh
for int i whilst i is less
than our inventory size i plus plus
and i'm going to get a clone system get
its uh inventory get its inventory slots
at position i and we're gonna assign the
item it corresponds to our inventories
um
inventory size so we could say uh this
dot inventory slots
i got data and this star inventory i or
inventory slots stack size i'm just
going to make that go on to a new line
so we can see that so we've got a clone
system and to
every inventory slot we're going to add
the corresponding slot on this on the
player's inventory
to this clone system so this is the
actual cloning of the player's inventory
inventory and now we need to go into a
for each loop i'm going to say for each
um i'm going to call this kvp for key
value pair
in our shopping cart dictionary we're
going to add one by one the items to the
player's inventory so
i'm gonna go into a for loop now so for
int i
whilst i is less than our key value pair
dot value so remember this shopping cart
takes in data and an amount of that data
so we've we've got cog is the data
and the player is trying to buy 30 cogs
from the shop we're going to go through
each of those 30 cards and try to add
them to the players
loaned inventory so if
cloned system got add to inventory i'm
going to pass in
the data
p
in this case
and the amount which is just
one because we're adding them in one by
one i'm going to return false so if we
fail to add this to the inventory system
then we're going to return false and
just as a refresher add to inventories
this
public bool method here
and this will return false if we don't
have a free slot so if it gets to him we
can't successfully add it to the
inventory system we're going to return
false so if we get to this point and we
can't add any more stuff to the clone
system we'll break out of the loop we'll
just return false
and then
that'll say that the player doesn't have
enough inventory to fit the shopping
cart in it and if it successfully loops
through all of this and completes
this method then we can just return true
we clearly do have enough
inventory space remaining
so then we can go to back to our
shopkeeper display and now this should
work so if we're selling oh if we're
selling or the player has enough
inventory space then we're just going to
return but if neither of them are met
then we're just going to set the basket
total text dot text to read not enough
room in inventory and then we can set
the basket total text dot color equal to
color dot red and there was a bit of an
error there and that was my mistake the
price can stay outside of this if
statement but the string can't
because we're trying to access the um
shopping cart
we're trying to access
uh the value which is at the shopping
cart dictionary but we don't know if
it's there yet until we get to this if
statement so let's just cut new string
and paste it back into our um if
statement and we'll do it twice and if
this is the first one to be added
to the shopping cart dictionary then we
can just say
x one because there's one item in the
dictionary and here we know that we
contain the key so then we can actually
access the key here so that should work
so let's go over to unity and make sure
that we've what we've just done is
actually all set up and working let's
hit play and we'll come over to this um
mpc here we'll press e
let's try and add some cogs to our
inventory and you can see here that as
we add them the player doesn't have
enough gold
so it's the total has gone red to kind
of indicate that we don't we can't
afford it that's adding stuff to the
basket currently we don't we can't get
any back out of the basket but you can
see that's working and we actually need
to use this modified price up here when
we add stuff to the
display so let's just add that quickly
so to do that we're going to go up to
the um display
shop inventory method here and we're
going to jump into this init function on
our shop slot ui script
and here
instead of setting it directly to the
assigned item slots um
gold value we can actually get the
modified price from our shopkeeper
display so let's do shop keeper display
and we made this static method so we can
we don't need to reference our parent we
can just do shopkeeper display get
modified
price and i've just realized that
we need to make this public so public
static in not private so that should
work here and i'm just going to put this
up
here so we'll do we'll make a new
variable so variable
modified price is equal and then we're
going to get the modified price
so remember this takes in um some data
so we can do the assigned item slot dot
item data
it takes in the amount of the item which
we just want um
one for now we're just going to show
kind of how much one costs and then we
can pass in
our markup so then here in the text we
can just pop in our modified price
instead of um the sort of base value so
that should be that so now we've got the
cart set up and working we want to be
able to actually buy the items when we
hit
the buy button we want to buy the car
and add it to the player's inventory and
take the gold from the player so let's
do that and i'm gonna i'm gonna move
this bool up to the top just to try and
keep everything sort of up here so
private ball is selling and here in
refresh display just before we click uh
just before we do clear slots
let's get um let's do some stuff with
the buy button to set it up so we can
actually buy the basket so it will say
if our buy button
is not equal to null then
we're going to set the buy button text
dot text
equal to and then here we're going to
use the is selling bool again so
are we selling an item or buying an item
are we selling our items to the shop or
we
buying items from the shop so we could
say is selling
if we are selling
it'll be sell items the button will say
and if we're not selling
uh we'll do buy items and maybe this
should be renamed to like the use cart
button instead of the buy button i'm
just gonna leave it called buy button
for now
um then i'm gonna get our buy button and
i'm going to remove all of the listeners
from the on click event and then we're
going to check if we're selling so
is selling
if we are selling we're going to add
the add a listener to the on click
button
and this is going to be a cell
items method that we're going to make
and then we'll do else
buy button dot on click dot add listener
buy items i'm gonna make a method called
buy items so every time we refresh the
display we're gonna change what the buy
button is doing which is this button
here we're gonna change what this button
does and says based on whether which tab
we've clicked up here um so let's make
these methods so we've got a private
void sell items and
we'll make a private void buy items
method and
we're not going to focus on selling
stuff at the minute
this video is already getting on quite
long
i just want to focus on being able to
buy the items and add them to the player
inventory so let's allow the player to
actually buy their basket and add it to
their inventory so
i'm going to say if the
layer inventory holder dot primary
system dot gold
is less than the basket
total then we're just going to return
with the buy button
doesn't need to do anything
uh we could just disable the buy button
based on this if we wanted but i'm going
to leave the button there and so the
player could click it but nothing will
happen if they don't have enough gold
for the
basket and then
we want to check if the
player inventory holder dot primary
inventory system dot
check imagery remaining
shopping cart
so we're gonna see if the player doesn't
have enough space for all of the items
in the basket
then we're just gonna return
and maybe this would be a bit more
performant if we used it as a
bowl if we keep a kind of a reference to
the result of that here so we're only
doing it once
um i mean that's up to you if you want
to do that i'm just going to leave it
like this for now um again i don't want
to get i don't want it to get too bogged
down with extra stuff and then we're
going to say four each avp
in
our shopping cart we're gonna purchase
the item from the shop so
shopsystem.purchase
item which again is a new method we're
going to need to make
which takes in a
key and an amount so let's make that
method over on our shop system script
we're going to make this purchase item
method and all this is going to do is um
i'm going to check whether we actually
contain the item which this is just a
fail safe we should we should have the
item in our inventory in we should have
the item in our inventory anyway because
we've you know we've added it to the
basket from our inventory but this is
just you know another sort of catch
all just to make sure that you know
nothing's gone wrong anywhere we don't
actually have the item for sale and then
we're just going to remove
from the slot and the other thing it
does is it gives us the slot back so if
this is true we still get this slot and
we can just say if we just say slot dot
remove from stack and pass in the
amount which is what i'm going to call
this so um
amount i'm going to rename that to data
instead of a new inventory item data i'm
just going to pass in data so
if we have the item in our inventory
we're going to add this amount to
so if we have the item in our shop's
inventory we're going to remove that
amount from the stack
if we don't we'll just return um because
you know like i said we don't want to
let the player buy something that the
shop doesn't have go back over to
shopkeeper display so we're going to buy
the item from the shop we're going to
add now the item to the player's
inventory so we could say 4 in i
whilst i is less than the key value pair
i plus plus
and then we're just going to add the
item to the player's inventory so play
inventory system dot add to inventory
kvp dot key and one because we're going
through one by one and we're adding them
all to the shop and then we're going to
um add the basket total
to the shop so the shop system is going
to gain gold passing in the basket total
and the player inventory holder our
primary inventory system
is going to spend some gold basket total
so let's make this gaingold method first
back over on the shop system script and
this is quite simple we're just going to
do available gold
minus equals plus equals the basket
total and
then let's make the spend gold method
over in our inventory system so spend
gold and that's simply just going to
minus from our gold basket total and
then back on our shops this uh
shopkeeper display
once we've done all of that we just need
to refresh the display again because
obviously stock has changed
so we can reflect the ui to
handle that so let's go over to our
project let's give our player some
money give them a payday so we've got
gold here let's set this to
um let's make him rich let's give him 5
000 gold actually no i want to show it
working um to show that the player
doesn't have enough gold for something
so
we're going to do gold 500
and let's go to our shop let's go to our
item scripts into the database
and the item data and let's make
something more expensive so what have we
got
so
swords 100 gold value 10 100 okay and
one so that's that's fine they're good
values so if we press play and we go
over to our shopkeeper
and we've now got our inventory system
here now got our shop system display
here we can add cogs to the basket and
the player
gold didn't update
let's fix that okay the reason that
didn't work is
when we create the inventory system here
we set the size to
uh
if we don't pass in the gold it'll just
reset it to zero so even though it's
um even though we put it in ahead of
time the inventory holder is kind of
overwriting that so what we need is we
just need a
serialized field and we can do a
protected
int gold and then when we create our
inventory system on the inventory holder
we can just pass in that gold amount and
the good thing about this is because
we're doing on the inventory holder not
the player inventory chests could have a
gold amount as well
um if you know you've got enemies and
they have loot on them they're going to
have an inventory system you can give
them gold for the player to get from the
um the enemies and stuff
um that should be
fine let's go back over and try this out
now so so it's not the inventory system
gold it's this gold that we need to
change so we'll do 500 gold here let's
press play and if we go back over to our
shop so we can now see the players got
500 gold
let's add
some cogs over
and you see that these uh
are reacting now with the markup value
so the health potions and the sword are
150 gold even though the base value was
a hundred
we can add
um these into the basket and then let's
get
some health potions as well you see that
we can't afford all of the health
potions so let's and i've forgotten that
we've not actually set up removing items
from the car as well we may as well get
that done now and it'll extend the video
just a little bit but not too much and
let's go back over to our shopkeeper
display and here we have
um do we have a remove item from car
method yet
remove iron from cart yeah let's move
this up
above um add-in to cart just so
we can go there okay so this is very
similar to the add item to cart but
we're kind of doing it in reverse so
we're going to get our data so var data
is equal to shop slot ui dot
assigned item slot dot item data and
then we're going to check does the
shopping cart
contain
data already if it does we're going to
reduce the value from we're going to
reduce the amount that the cart holds by
one we're going to get the modified
price so it's going to copy this
underneath data here we're going to copy
the new string as well and in fact let's
just copy all of this so i'm going to
copy the new string in the shopping cart
ui at the data and if we reduce the
amount of the item in the cart to zero
so if shopping cart data shopping cart
data
is less than or equal to zero and we're
going to call shopping cart
dot remove
r
because it's no longer in the car we're
going to get a reference to the game
object of our shopping cart text so
equal to shopping cart
ui data dot game object we're going to
remove the shopping cart ui from the
shopping cart ui
dictionary so shopping cart ui
dot remove the data key
and then we're going to destroy
our temp
obj so here we instantiate it when we
add it to the cart and then when we
remove it completely from the cart we're
going to destroy it and then we're going
to say that if the basket total is less
than or then we need to modify the
basket total so we can do um basket
total
minus equals the price we can update the
basket total text to reflect the new
um total amount so total
basket total
g and then we're going to say if the
basket total is less than or equal to
zero and
the basket total text is active and
we're just going to hide the text so
basket total
x dot enabled is equal to false
we'll hide the buy button so buy button
dot game object
dot set active do false we're going to
clear the item preview which is we've
not implemented the item preview section
yet we'll do that in the next video but
let's make that method now ahead of that
and then finally we're going to check
the cart verse available
gold and we only need to do that if we
haven't just uh set it to active so
let's just return here if the bass if
there's nothing left in the basket let's
return cause there's nothing left in the
shopping cart so we don't need to check
it against available gold so hopefully
you followed along with that because it
is just the kind of the reverse of what
we're doing down here
let's go back over to unity and
hopefully oh wait let's just check one
more thing sorry
we need to go over to the shop slot ui
go to our remove item from cart
method on the shop slot ui um and okay
we've already set that up so that's fine
i just wanted to check that so let's go
back over to unity hit play over to our
shop
car
our shop npc here let's add some cogs
let's try and remove them okay so you
can see that we can now add and remove
things from our basket let's add in you
know some potions okay we can't afford
that many potions we can afford this
many we'll hit buy that buys the items
it adds the amount to the shops gold
it decreases the player's gold and now
if we go
back which i've just realized we still
can't close the shop panel let me just
manually close that
shop controller ui okay so you know we
can see that we've got the four cogs and
three potions in the players inventory
so i know that was very very long-winded
and i apologize um hopefully you follow
along with it
if you want the project files for this
video they are available over on
patreon.com forward slash danpos i'd
just like to take a minute to thank all
of my patrons on screen now we can see
the 10 000 xp tier which is a sector
sweep and i want to thank all of the 4
000 xp tier members as well if you want
any help with this video or any of the
other videos on my channel feel free to
leave a comment below or better yet join
the discord server which is linked in
the description but for now thanks for
watching and i'll catch you in the next
one bye hello and welcome to today's
video
you